ag.org 2019-05-05

# Assemblies of God (USA) Official Web Site | Privacy

As The General Council of the Assemblies of God, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not give, sell, rent or loan any identifiable information regarding visitors to any third party. By using our web site, ag.org, you agree to the Privacy Policy of The General Council of the Assemblies of God. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this web site.

The General Council of the Assemblies of God reviews its Privacy Policy periodically and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. This Privacy Policy applies to all web sites produced and maintained by The General Council of the Assemblies of God. 

If you want to communicate with us about our Privacy Policy, e-mail us at [info@ag.org](mailto:info@ag.org), or write us at: The General Council of the Assemblies of God, Office of Public Relations, 1445 N. Boonville Avenue, Springfield, MO 65802.

### Collection and Use

The General Council of the Assemblies of God recognizes the privacy concerns of users of our web site and the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected from them. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as a visitor’s name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, or credit card information is automatically collected on our web site. Such information is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted, and The General Council of the Assemblies of God uses such information only for the purpose for which it was submitted, unless we disclose other uses in this policy or at the time of collection.

We maintain reasonable and appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of such information in our possession. The General Council of the Assemblies of God does not sell, trade or rent personally identifiable information to third parties. We reserve the right to monitor traffic patterns and web site usage.

### Security

When submitting sensitive data like credit card information, we use secure server technology to protect the information. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts the information you input before you send it to us. All of the data is protected against unauthorized access, as indicated by the secure icon on your browser.

### Cookies

"Cookies" are files that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information about a user. They enable us to provide customized features to enhance your visit to the web site. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Users should consult their browser help files for instructions on how to refuse cookies.

### Links

This web site may be linked to or from other web sites that are not operated by The General Council of the Assemblies of God or any affiliates. The General Council of the Assemblies of God is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these third party web sites. This web site may also be linked to web sites operated by organizations affiliated with the General Council. Visitors to those web sites should refer to their separate privacy policies and practices.
